

PROFILE

I'm a Boston-based UX/UI researcher and designer who is focused on incorporating empathy, strategy and iteration in my design solutions to user problems. As a kid I was always coloring, painting, drawing and sketching — design is part of my core. As an adult I was drawn to user experience design because of the ever-changing nature of products, and the user needs that drive those changes.

EXPERIENCE

UX/UI Design Intern

Forrester • Boston, MA • August 2017 – Present

Conducting and utilizing user research to make informed design decisions. Creating high and low fidelity prototypes and testing prototypes to make iterative changes supported by user and business objectives.

• Forrester's Contact Us Page

Performed 1-on-1 user testing and ideated with Mgr. UX Design. Designed a strategic plan, wireframes and prototype for testing.

• Forrester's Search Page

Designed a Usability Research Test Plan and conducted Usability testing. Synthesized research to inform iterative designs with Mgr. UX Design.

• Forrester's Mobile App

Designed a Usability Research Test Plan and conducted usability testing. Synthesized research to inform future designs with team of 3.

Program Manager

Forrester • Boston, MA • January 2016 - Present

Drive projects by defining scope and developing project plans, tracking milestones, ensuring deadlines are met, and facilitating internal and external expectations and communication.

EDUCATION

General Assembly

User Experience Design • New York City, NY • June 2018

Attended accelerated design program and learned to unpack design-thinking to solve user's needs. Focused on next generation mobile/web applications in the digital space.

Suffolk University

Master of Public Administration - Business • Boston, MA • 2012 - 2013

University of Massachusetts - Lowell

Bachelor of Arts - Political Science • Lowell, MA • 2007 - 2012

CONTACT

drewkayla.com Drew.KaylaA@gmail.com 978 • 204 • 5521 in/kayladrew

SKILLS

User interviews
User Interface design
Affinity Mapping
Personas
Wireframing
Prototyping
Usability testing
Interface Architecture

TOOLS

Expert

Sketch User Testing InVision Principle Axure RP Procreate

Intermediate

HTML5 Illustrator CSS3 Photoshop

Exploring

Zeplin InDesign

INTERESTING FACT

I'm a competitive ultimate frisbee player on one of the top teams in Boston! I compete in tournaments across the country during the summer and spend my winters training hard for the each new season.